Friends who have not bought a policy from me, but it also happens like this, it is
okay, later they
also did it, your friends are
very useful in supporting you, your social circle is very
useful, because you need to put your point across,
how are you working, what are you
giving them, what are you telling them in their life,
what can happen to them and the day you get the claim,
if you get two or four claims, then it comes
with the amount, you have to
calculate it yourself, that is the only problem,
you just calculate it from your data or your head and
publish it, then the number comes,
[Music] and you
can follow the annual report there, the
second thing is that I say that
friend, if I interview you for ICICI